By the time you graduate from your Nanodegree program,
你从纳诺度学院毕业的时候
you'll have mastered relevant skills and learned to work independently.
你就会掌握相关技能并学会独立工作
And we want to help you get there, as efficiently as possible.
我们想帮助你尽可能高效地得到帮助
That's why we focus on learning by doing.
这就是为什么我们注重学习的原因
To graduate, you'll complete a series of milestones,
毕业后你将完成一系列的里程碑
most of which will take the form of projects.
其中大部分将采取项目的形式
You can prepare for these projects by taking your courses,
你可以通过你的课程来为这些项目做准备
although reviewing all of the course material isn't a graduation requirement.
虽然审查所有的课程材料都不是毕业要求
If you've come in with a ton of prior experience,
如果你有一顿之前的经历
feel free to try jumping right into the projects.
可以随意跳进项目中
However, most students go through the course material thoroughly
不过 大多数学生都是通过课程材料
to make sure they have the skills and
确保他们有能力
knowledge they need to be successful in their projects and beyond.
他们需要在项目和其他领域取得成功 。这意味着我会在这里和那里弹出来为您正在学习的内容提供更多背景信息。